JACK WITBROCK FINLAY

LOCATION: Auckland, New Zealand

PHONE: +64 22 603 5912 EMAIL: jack@jackfinlay.com

WEB: jackfinlay.com

GITHUB: github.com/JackWFinlay

Summary

Successful career in software development with five years of professional experience. Skilled in full-stack .NET, Cloud, and database development. Constantly seeking to further skills and education through independent study.

Technical Skills

Skill	Experience
C#, ASP.NET, .NET Framework & .NET Core, JavaScript	5 years
SQL	4 years
Version Control (Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Azure DevOps)	5 years
Databases (SQL Server, Oracle, CosmosDB, DocumentDB)	4 Years
Agile Methodologies (SCRUM, Kanban)	4 Years
Agile Tools (Atlassian Jira, Azure DevOps)	3 Years

Education

Auckland University of Technology, Auckland, New Zealand 2013 - 2016

 Bachelor of Computer and Information Science - Software Development Major.

Topics covered included: Software Development in C# and Java, Object-Oriented Design and Development, Databases, Agile Methodologies, Information security, Data process Modelling, Project Management, Discrete Mathematics and Linear Algebra, Data Structures, and Algorithms.

Experience

Software Engineer

Plexure Ltd, Auckland. January 2019 - Present

- C#, ASP.NET Core, .NET Framework
- Azure Cloud, AWS Cloud

Responsible for producing .NET Core and Framework solutions on platform optimisation projects for globally reaching products. Programming in C#, and using Azure and AWS cloud platforms and technologies.

Software Developer

AlphaCert Labs Ltd, Auckland. March 2018 - January 2019

- C#, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework
- Microsoft SQL Server T-SQL development

Full-stack ASP.Net MVC development. Primarily C#, HTML/CSS, and JavaScript. ETL and data transformation in C# with MEF. T-SQL database development, database migrations via Fluent Migrator.

Analyst Programmer

Gentrack Ltd, Auckland. August 2016 - March 2018

- BASIC Variant
- Analysis, Debugging
- Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle Database development

Defect fixes and extension of functionality of utilities billing software. Data analysis and database development using SQL. Collaboration with internal and external clients to achieve consistent results.

Technical Consultant

Business Mechanix Ltd, Auckland. April 2015 - August 2016

- C#, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework
- SPARQL RDF API
- Microsoft SQL Server development

Developed a website for international students to find study options in New Zealand. Managed and mentored a team of three interns working over the 2015/16 summer. Setup and managed Azure virtual machines, maintenance of C# applications, and ad-hoc customer support.

Intern Developer

University of Auckland IT Services, Auckland. December 2014 - February 2015

• Java, Scriptella, Bash

Intern developer role at IT Services. Existing and new projects. Developed an HTTP driver for Scriptella from the source code. Various ad-hoc Scriptella, Groovy and Bash scripts.

References

References available upon request